reaconverter.com 2014-12-30

# reasoft | Privacy policy

Privacy Policy:

ReaSoft Development has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

We at ReaSoft are aware of the growing concern of internet users regarding the widespread distribution of their personal information, and are taking measures to protect our customer's and visitor's privacy. We do not sell or redistribute our e-mail lists to third parties or spammers. 

The information submitted, whether it is a purchase, a download of a demo product, or simply joining our mailing list, remains confidential and is for our records only. We keep this information so that we can notify customers of product upgrades, announcements, and new releases. If a customer/user does not wish to receive this information, they can manually request to be removed from our mailing lists at any point simply by sending unsubscribe mail, that includes from end of all e-mails. And we never add our customers to our mailing lists after any contacts us. They can subscribe to our mailing lists manually. 

In order to further protect customer information, all order forms are run on a secure server, utilizing encryption technology to safeguard all transactions (credit card/online purchases) from unauthorized viewing. It is used standard SSL encryption, with a certificate from VeriSign. 

This site contains links to other sites. ReaSoft Development is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

These measures, along with our belief that it is up to the individual to determine who receives and what may be done with their personal information, insure that any information submitted on our site will be kept confidential. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us. 

|     | 

additional info

* Contact ReaSoft
 
* Info for journalists
 
* ReaSoft Image Converter

News-list:

product updates, new releases
